# Tran Quang Vu

## Front-End Developer

★ tranquangvu1008@gmail.com

**\** 0852602740

● 01G, DT743A Street, Noi Hoa 2 Quarter, Binh An Ward, Di An City, Binh Duong Province

#### **SUMMARY STATEMENT**

At the age of 24, I have 2 years of software development experience with many different languages and platforms such as HTML/CSS/JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJS, Flutter, AWS, Git. Confident communication and willingness to devote myself to work are my next strengths to create valuable and quality products.

## **SKILLS**

#### **Hard Skills**

- Programming Language: HTML CSS/SCSS JavaScript/TypeScript | Dart
- Frameworks && Tools: ReactJS | NextJS | Redux/Redux Toolkit/Redux Saga | Ant Design | Tailwind CSS | Flutter | Firebase | Cloudinary | AWS | Git | Jenkins | Jira
- Language: Vietnamese (native); English (Intermediate)

#### **Soft Skills**

- Critical Thinking and Problem Solving | Time Management | Debugging Situation
- Diagnose | Analytical Skills | Debating | Teamwork

#### **CERTIFICATES**

React – The Complete Guide 2023 (incl. React Router & Redux) by Udemy

Redux Saga with React: Fast-track Redux Saga intro course by Udemy

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## RAVER.VN 2.0 (No deadline)

Feb 2024 - Now

Freelancer NextJS Developer

Project to improve the website of a large Electronic Dance Music Community in Vietnam. Bringing a new interface with outstanding features to attract and reach domestic and foreign music lovers.

- Program the application's interface using NextJS.
- Upgrade new features to increase user experience.
- Restful API through Wordpress.

Technology: NextJS (HTML/CSS/JavaScript), TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Wordpress, Gitlab, Docker, Trello.

#### FPT Software (AIRFORCE1 – KANSAI AIRPORT GROUP)

Apr 2022 - Dec 2023

Front-end Developer and Devops

Core project of Kansai Airport Group (Japan). The system created to manage the group's projects and contracts is abbreviated as IRCA (Investment, Running, Contract, Approval).

- Program the application's interface using ReactJS.
- Gained practical experience interface in web development using HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript.
- Supported to Backend developer to fetch API and to display data via the screen of device.
- Component performance optimization for a wide range of web- capable devices and browsers.
- Participated in code reviews and learned best practices for writing clean, maintainable, and well-documented code.
- Lead a team of 5 members, working together to ensure the quality of the source code before planning deployment and uploading it to the server.
- Set up AWS services and CI/CD tool to operate the project to achieve the best efficiency.
- Provide guidance and problem solving to team members to develop their skills and ensure success.

Technology: ReactJS (HTML/CSS/JavaScript), TypeScript, Ant Design, AWS, Gitlab, Jenkins, Nginx, Jira.

## FPT Software (WR\_LIFEAPP - WOORIEN)

Jun 2021 - Nov 2021

Intern Mobile Developer

Dog care application of Woorien Company (Korea). The application was created to care for and train dogs through exercise videos from basic to complex.

- Program the application's interface using Flutter.
- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Use Bloc Pattern to manage state for the project.
- Research and install new Flutter packages.

Technology: Flutter (Dart), Gitlab, Jira.

#### **PROJECT**

#### vite-my-profile (devu.blog) ⊘

Technology: ReactJS + Vite | Ant Design | Tailwind CSS

#### react-user *⊘*

Technology: ReactJS + Vite | React Hook Form | Tailwind CSS

## **EDUCATION**

## **FPT University (Vietnam)**

2018 - 2022

Software Engineering (GPA: 7.3)